[
    {
        "front": "かわる",
        "back": "代わる \nto substitute",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "じだい",
        "back": "時代 \nera",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "ガスだい",
        "back": "ガス代 \ngas-bill",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "つかう",
        "back": "使う \nto use",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "しよう",
        "back": "使用 \nto use",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "しようちゅう",
        "back": "使用中 \nin use",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "たいしかん",
        "back": "大使館 \nembassy",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "つくる",
        "back": "作る \nto make",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "さくひん",
        "back": "作品 \nmasterpiece",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "さくぶん",
        "back": "作文 \nparagraph",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "さっか",
        "back": "作家 \nauthor",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "さぎょう",
        "back": "作業 \noperate",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぶんか",
        "back": "文化 \nculture",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "かがく",
        "back": "化学 \nchemistry",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "へんか",
        "back": "変化 \nchange, transformation",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんじる",
        "back": "信じる \nto believe",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんごう",
        "back": "信号 \ntraffic signal",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "じしん",
        "back": "自信 \nself-confidence",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "すすむ",
        "back": "進む \nto proceed",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんぽ",
        "back": "進歩 \nprogress",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "せんしんこく",
        "back": "先進国 \ndeveloped country",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "おくる",
        "back": "送る \nto send",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "そうしん",
        "back": "送信 \nto send an email",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "そうきん",
        "back": "送金 \nsending money",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほうそう",
        "back": "放送 \nbrodcasting",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "かえす",
        "back": "返す \nto return",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "へんじ",
        "back": "返事 \nreply",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "へんしん",
        "back": "返信 \nreply (of a mail etc.)",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "くりかえす",
        "back": "繰り返す \nrepeat",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "あらう",
        "back": "洗う \nto wash",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "せんたく",
        "back": "洗濯 \nwashing clothes",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "おてあらい",
        "back": "お手洗い \nwashroom",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "そそぐ",
        "back": "注ぐ \nto pour",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうもん",
        "back": "注文 \nto order",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうい",
        "back": "注意 \ncaution",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    },
    {
        "front": "えいがか",
        "back": "映画化 \nfilm adaptation",
        "chapter": "N4 K15"
    }
]